bookingbuddy.co.uk 2005-02-03

# Booking Buddy - Airfare, Hotel Rate, and Car Rental Rate Comparison Tool

_This Privacy Policy was last changed January 2, 2004._

## Overview 

The following Privacy Policy explains how BookingBuddy.com. ("Booking Buddy") gathers and uses personal information that is provided by our customers. Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and Booking Buddy reserves the right to change or modify our Privacy Policy at any time with or without notice.

_Booking Buddy is committed to safeguarding your privacy. We do not rent or sell our customer database or newsletter subscriber list to third parties._ We do not share customer information in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.

If you have any questions or concerns over the Booking Buddy Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact [privacy@bookingbuddy.com](mailto:privacy@bookingbuddy.com).

By accessing a Booking Buddy publication or by subscribing to a Booking Buddy newsletter, you agree to our current [Terms of Use](http://www.bookingbuddy.com/terms.php).

## Site Registration

Booking Buddy's registration form may, in the future, require users to provide basic contact and demographic information. We use or may use your contact information (such as e-mail address) from the registration form to send you newsletters and occasional information about our services and partners, inform you if you are the potential winner of a contest or promotion, personalize your experience with Booking Buddy, or investigate cases of suspected fraud or abuse. You may opt-out of receiving future communications; see the Opting-Out of Further Communications section below. 

In the future, in order to customize your experience with our e-mail newsletters, we may receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Booking Buddy if your computer supports such capabilities. Clicking on a link in a Booking Buddy newsletter may also be tracked on a per user basis to allow us to present content, which closely matches your interests. Demographic and profile data (such as state, zip code, age, or gender) may be used to customize your experience at our site or in our e-mail newsletters, showing you content and advertising that may best suit your needs. This information is shared with advertisers and other third parties on an aggregate basis only. _Individual user click behavior is never shared with third parties._

If, in the future, you enter Booking Buddy via a reward or incentive program, Booking Buddy may share your e-mail address with the program through which you entered Booking Buddy to ensure you are credited with your incentive. 

You may, in the future, also register for Booking Buddy and/or specific Booking Buddy newsletters at web sites operated by third parties. These third parties may share contact, demographic or profile data that you voluntarily provide during the registration process with Booking Buddy. Booking Buddy does or may in the future use this information in the same manner as information collected directly by Booking Buddy. This Privacy Policy does not bind sites that collect information on behalf of Booking Buddy, and Booking Buddy is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. 

To better serve you, we may also store information you present to us via e-mail or telephone communications with Booking Buddy's Customer Service Department. This information is or may be used in the same manner as information directly collected using Booking Buddy's registration form. We may also use information you provide us via e-mail or telephone to pursue the matter for which you contacted us. Booking Buddy also may obtain information from you in our online forums. This information may not be disclosed except as consistent with Terms of Use. 

In order to better communicate with registered users about their registration status, Booking Buddy may acquire information about users from third-party sources, including but not limited to a users mailing address. The information collected will only be shared, if at all, on an aggregate basis only with third parties. 

E-mail Communications: To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Booking Buddy if your computer supports such capabilities.

## Data Sharing

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

Booking Buddy may use third parties to perform certain tasks such as package delivery. Personal information may be provided to these agents as is necessary to perform their functions. 

Booking Buddy partners with third-party companies to provide services to Booking Buddy users. When you sign up for one of these services, the information you provide in signing up for the service is shared with the third party and is protected in accordance with the third party's Privacy Policy. 

In the future, Booking Buddy may host content on behalf of certain other web site partners. These pages will be identified as they have the navigation of the partner site. Information collected on these pages may be shared with the partner site. These pages, and any information shared with the partner site, are subject to the Privacy Policy of the partner site. 

Occasionally, Booking Buddy may participate in reward programs. In order to properly credit you for your reward, we may share basic customer information with the reward-giver.

## Sweepstakes, Online Surveys, and Order Forms

Booking Buddy occasionally runs sweepstakes, hosts online surveys, or uses order forms on our web site in which we ask for contact and demographic information. Participation in sweepstakes and surveys and usage of order forms is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. We use or may use your contact information (such as e-mail address) from your sweepstakes entry, survey registration, or order form to inform you if you are the potential winner of a contest or promotion, personalize your experience with Booking Buddy, send you newsletters (should you opt-in for these newsletters) and occasional information about our services or partners, or investigate cases of suspected fraud. You may opt-out of receiving future communications; see the Opting-Out of Further Communications section below. 

Demographic and profile data (such as zip code, age, or gender) may be used to customize your experience at our site, showing you content and advertising that may best suit your needs. This information is shared with advertisers and other third parties on an aggregate basis only. In the event that Booking Buddy partners with a third party to run a sweepstakes, Booking Buddy may share demographic and profile data with such third party only as indicated in the official sweepstakes rules. 

## Tell-a-Friend and E-mail This Deal

Booking Buddy may, from time to time, offer services to allow our users to send information about our site to their friends. If a user elects to use such service for informing a friend about our site, or elects to use our other services to inform a friend about information on our site, we will ask them for the friend's e-mail address. We will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit our site. We store this information for the purpose of sending this one-time e-mail and investigating suspected fraud. 

## Children Under 13 Years Old

We do not use our web site to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13. Children under 13 may not participate in any online activities on the Booking Buddy site. 

## IP Addresses

Booking Buddy uses IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our web site, and help diagnose problems with our servers. IP addresses are also used to gather broad demographic information and to prevent, investigate, and take actions in the case of suspected fraud or abuse. 

## Cookies

A cookie is a small piece of data that a web server places on a user's computer. Booking Buddy employs the use of cookies to ensure that you do not see the same ad repeatedly, to track marketing promotions, to estimate and report audience size and traffic, and to customize and personalize your experience at BookingBuddy.com.

Furthermore, Booking Buddy may, from time to time, use outside media companies to display advertisements on our site. These ads may contain cookies, which are collected and tracked by the outside media company. Booking Buddy has no access to or control over these cookies.

Most web browsers provide users the ability to limit the use of cookies by allowing users to adjust privacy settings. If a user has their cookies disabled, Booking Buddy will still be accessible, however some sections of the web site will not perform as well as they normally would with cookies enabled.

## Links to Other Sites

BookingBuddy.com contains links to other web sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of every web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

## Security, Fraud, and Abuse

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Booking Buddy regularly reviews these measures to better protect users. Occasionally information may be provided to Booking Buddy fraudulently or by an individual unauthorized to provide such information. Booking Buddy may use all information it collects for reasonable investigation and prosecution of suspected fraud and/or abuse. Booking Buddy may provide all information it collects to third parties as necessary to comply with law enforcement requests or other legal requirements. 

Booking Buddy does not ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet.

## Opting Out of Further Communications and Updating Personal Information

BookingBuddy.com subscribers may opt out of receiving future BookingBuddy.com communications or update their personal information using any of the following methods:

  * Website: <http://www.bookingbuddy.com/sub/changesubscriptions.php>
  * E-mail: [help@bookingbuddy.com](mailto:help@bookingbuddy.com)
  * Mail: Smarter Living, Inc., Attn: Booking Buddy Customer Service, 465 Medford Street, Suite 400 Boston, MA 02129

To opt out of future communications from Booking Buddy's partners, please contact the partner directly. For assistance with this, please contact Booking Buddy's Customer Service: [help@bookingbuddy.com](mailto:help@bookingbuddy.com).

## Service and Partner Updates

We may send our users service and partner announcements from time to time. Users are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain information about our services and partners, without opting-out of all Booking Buddy newsletters. You may opt-out of receiving future communications; see the Opting-Out of Further Communications section below. 

We communicate with our users to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via e-mail, telephone, or postal mail. 

## Notification of Changes

If at any point we decide to share personally identifiable information to third parties FOR REASONS NOT OUTLINED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, we will notify our users by way of an e-mail, so that users are made aware. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. 

## Smarter Living Product

BookingBuddy.com is a product managed by Smarter Living, Inc. Smarter Living, Inc. from time to time may compare, merge or append information collected on BookingBuddy.com with data from one or more other sites managed by Smarter Living, Inc. Similarly, information you provide on other Smarter Living, Inc. managed sites may be compared, merged or appended to information you provide via BookingBuddy.com.

## Business Assets 

As part of operations, Booking Buddy may sell, transfer or merge particular businesses and/or other assets to a third party. As part of such a transaction, personal information users have provided to Booking Buddy may be given to a third party. Booking Buddy attempts to comply with all legislative and judicial orders. These orders will take precedence over the details stated in the policy above. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or your dealings with Booking Buddy, please contact: 

Smarter Living, Inc.  
465 Medford Street  
Suite 400  
Boston, MA 02129  
617-886-5555  
617-886-5501 (fax)
